eventmanagerblog.com 2019-05-25

# Privacy Policy & Terms of Use

**1\. Introduction**  
EventManagerBlog.com or EventMB is owned and operated by Social Coup LLC, a company incorporated in the State of Nevada, USA. This privacy policy and Terms of Use set out the basis on which any personal data that we have collected about you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

This is the privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) that governs how we, EventMB (“we”, “our” or “us”), use Personal Data (defined below) that we collect, receive and store about individuals in connection with the use of: (i) the websites at www.eventmanagerblog.com and any other website under the eventmanagerblog.com domain that we operate (collectively, together with their sub-domains, content and services, the “Sites”).

We ourselves do not host any of the Sites and Service. All hosting is done by third-party service providers that we engage. This means that data you provide us or that we collect from you (including any Personal Data, as defined below) – as further described in this Privacy Policy – is hosted with such third-party service providers on servers that they own or control. Regardless of where such third-party service providers are located, their servers may be located anywhere in the world. Your data may even be replicated across multiple servers located in multiple countries.

We review this privacy policy regularly. Occasionally we may need to make changes or additions to this privacy policy that may affect how we handle your data. We will post new versions of this privacy policy on our website (the “Site”). We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors and readers; in this policy we explain how we will treat your personal information.

This Privacy Policy has been updated to ensure compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) coming into effect on May 25, 2018 and affecting residents of the EU and European Economic Area (EEA).

 **2\. Collecting personal data and When we collect it**  
You are not legally obligated to provide us Personal Data and may do so at your own free will. If you do not agree to provide us with such data or have it processed by us or any of our authorized third parties or service providers, please simply do not enter our Sites or use our Service. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time at our discretion. Such change will be effective seven (7) days following posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Sites, and your continued use of the Service thereafter means that you accept those changes. For changes affecting opt-ins you will be asked to expressly give your consent.

2.1 When we collect your personal data:  
We receive and collect Personal Data from you when you provide us your information to signup to our newsletters, when you download our resources (reports, ebooks, guides), when you contact us for sales inquiries, when you submit your company and product information for inclusion in our ebooks and reports, when you sign up to our events, when you sign up to our CMP portal, when you sign up to our Insights platform, when you contact us for a general inquiry or when you make a purchase and provide your billing information.

We receive and collect Personal Data from your browser or mobile device about your use of the Sites and Service. We use log files and analytics tools to analyze trends, administer the Sites and Service, track users’ movement around the Sites and Service, and gather statistical data. We use “cookies”, technical identifiers and Pixels in order to provide and enhance our Sites and Service. We also collect limited data regarding your system and device, such as your mobile device id or browser preferences.

We receive and collect Personal Data from Third Parties, such as service providers, ad networks and marketing agencies, or from Services Integrations when you use third party integrations.

2.2 What personal data we collect or may collect:  
(a) anonymous information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths);  
(b) information that you provide to us when registering with our website;  
(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters (including your name and email address);  
(e) information that you provide to us when using the services on our website, or that is generated in the course of the use of those services (including the timing, frequency and pattern of service use);  
(f) information relating to any purchases you make of our services or any other transactions that you enter into through our website (including your name, address, telephone number, email address and card details);  
(g) information contained in or relating to any communications that you send to us or send through our website (including the communication content and meta data associated with the communication);  
(i) any other personal information that you choose to send to us; and  
(j) information contained in opt-in forms, that might also be used by authorized third parties with your express consent  
(k) anonymous cookie ID, Advertising ID, and/or device ID to segment user groups for marketing purposes, and to execute retargeting campaigns in order to deliver personalised advertising by EventMB or authorized third parties  
(l) Pixel tags that tell us what parts of the website have been visited or measure the effectiveness of searches users perform on the website. We may also use pixel tags in email messages to tell us whether emails have been opened to assure that we are only sending messages that are of interest to our users.

2.2 Before you disclose to us the personal information of another person, you must obtain that person's consent to both the disclosure and the processing of that personal information in accordance with this policy.

 **3\. How we use your personal data**  
Personal information submitted to us through our Sites and resources, including digital publications and webinars, will be used for the purposes specified in this policy or on the relevant pages of the websites or individual resources.

We may use your personal information to:  
(a) supply to you services purchased, subscribed to or requested through our websites, including but not limited to the  
(b) accessing resources you requested to read or download;  
(c) send you notifications about events you have registered or requested to attend;  
(d) send you notifications about CMP resources and events if you have subscribed to our CMP portal;  
(e) send you email notifications that you have specifically requested;  
(f) send you our email newsletters, if you have requested it (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require the newsletter);  
(g) send you marketing communications relating to our business (or the businesses of trusted and fully disclosed third-parties) which we think may be of interest to you, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications);  
(h) transmitting your data to the Event Industry Council following your application for credits on our CMP Portal;  
(i) send statements, invoices and payment reminders to you, and collect payments from you;  
(j) send you relevant communications that we have a legitimate interest in sending you;  
(k) provide third parties with statistical information about our users;  
(l) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to our website;  
(m) keep our website secure and prevent fraud;

3.1 If you submit personal information for publication on our websites, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the licence you grant to us.

 **4\. Disclosing personal information**  
We may disclose your personal information:  
(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;  
(b) in connection with any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings;  
(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);  
(d) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset that we are (or are contemplating) selling; and  
(e) to any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information.  
(f) to authorized third parties (sponsors) when you submit your data to access our resources, including but not limited to ebooks, webinars, reports. You will be informed of the sponsors' names at signup.  
(g) to business partners and affiliates, so they can contact you in order to offer or promote our products and services

Except as provided in this policy, we will not provide your personal information to third parties.

 **5\. Outside links**  
8.1 Our website includes hyperlinks to, and details of, third party websites.  
8.2 We have no control over, and are not responsible for, the privacy policies and practices of third parties.

 **6\. Cookies and Pixels**  
6.1 Cookies are information packets sent by web servers to web browsers, and stored by the web browsers.  
6.2 The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables a web server to identify and track web browsers.  
6.3 There are two main kinds of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser, whereas persistent cookies remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach their expiry date.  
6.4 Cookies on Our Website. Event Manager Blog uses the following cookies on  
this website, for the following purposes:  
(a) Social Media Cookies  
(b) Google Analytics Cookies  
(c) Ecommerce Cookies  
(d) Facebook pixel  
(e) Nimble pixel  
(f) Yesware pixel  
6.5 Google Cookies. Event Manager Blog uses Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store and use this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.] 6.4 Refusing Cookies. Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies.  
(a) In Internet Explorer, you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.  
(b) In Firefox, you can adjust your cookies settings by clicking “Tools”, “Options” and “Privacy”.  
6.5 Blocking cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of our websites.

 **7\. Remarketing**  
We may use Google’s remarketing service to target our or third party's ads to you based on your prior use of the Site when you visit on other sites in Google Display or Search Network.

 **8\. Security of your personal information**  
8.1 We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.  
8.2 You acknowledge that the transmission of information over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.  
8.3 You are responsible for keeping any password you should use for accessing our website confidential; we will not ask you for your password (except when you log in to our website).

 **9\. How long we keep your personal data**  
Your information we use for marketing purposes will be kept with us until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive this information.

 **10\. Amendments**  
10.1 We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website.  
10.2 You should check this page occasionally to ensure you agree with any changes to this policy.

 **11\. Your rights**  
You will be asked to expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal information for the purposes outlined in this Policy. We always provide you with an opportunity to opt out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes, cancel your subscriptions, delete your profile, delete your data altogether. Please let us know if you wish to update or delete the personal data we hold about you by emailing us at contact @ eventmanagerblog.com or simply unsubscribe from any email where an unsubscribe or opt-out link is provided.

 **12\. Children’s Privacy**  
Our Sites and services are not structured to attract children under the age of 16, and we do not intend to collect Personal Data from anyone we know to be under 16. If we learn that we have collected Personal Data from anyone under 16 years, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any such information, please contact us at  
contact @ eventmanagerblog.com

 **13\. Our details**  
12.1 This website is owned and operated by Social Coup LLC.  
12.2 We are registered in State of Nevada.  
12.3 You can contact us by using our website contact form or by email to ‘contact @ eventmanagerblog.com’

Last reviewed: May 15, 2018.
